# 我们这个小龙虾现在已经刷了很多次了（很多只了）
We have been cleaning these crayfish for several times
# 这个水特别的黑
The water here are turning black
# 所以我之前拍的那个“麻辣小龙虾”刷6遍一点都不夸张
See? When I said that I had to clean 6 times in my previous video, I was not joking.
# 今天我们准备了这个小龙虾 你看10斤
Today, we have 5 kg of crayfish
# 10斤现在已经洗了第一遍
This is after the first round of cleaning
# 大家看一下这个水 黑成什么样子
Look at the color, how dark it is
# 这新买的刷子都变黑了
Even the brand new brush is turning black.
# 我们切青瓜这样子切
Here’s how I chop the cucumber
# 竖下来切一条
First slice it in half
# 每一边切三条 这样子走下来
And then slice each half into three strips.
# 然后就切成条了
Then we chop them into pieces
# 大蒜放多一点
Be generous with the garlic
# 这个的话整个的也可以 切下来也行
You can either use them like this, or chop them into small pieces
# 刚才拿这个黄瓜的时候不小心刮到一下手
I accidentally cut myself when I was preparing the cucumbers
# 这里破了点皮
A small cut here
# 切这个小米辣 所以我要把这个弄上
I had to cover it with Band-Aid because I am now chopping the chili peppers
# 因为刚哥的手也是有感觉的好不好
Because, hey, I do have feelings on my fingers.
# 之前说抓辣椒没感觉
Some fans were joking that I don’t feel the chilis at all on my figners
# 这个伤口抓辣椒感觉不是一般的好
Well, it feels very “nice” on the wounds like this
# 今天呢我们准备了一些魔芋
We also have some Konjac here
# 魔芋在我们四川啊 人人都爱吃
Everyone loves Konjac in Sichuan
# 只不过我四伯爷不爱吃
Except my uncle
# 待会儿他可能不会吃这个魔芋
So he will probably skip this later
# 漆二娃 你来吃撒
Have a taste Qi Erwa
# 先你都在说你口水都流出来了安
You were saying that you were already drooling
# 漆二娃吃这个龙虾我要拜你为师哦
Qi Erwa you are the real master of Eating a crayfish
# 嗯 对
Of course
# 你吃龙虾还是老师噶
You have to teach us
# 我们这个小龙虾之前很多粉丝说做这个太麻烦了
Some followers were saying that it was quite complicated to cook crayfish
# 黄瓜可以吃都嘛
(Can I also eat the cucumber?)
# 可以
Sure
# 然后我现在把这些料全部搞在一个小包装里面
Now I have prepared all the ingredients in one package
# 你们拿回去直接煮就可以了
So you can just cook them directly at home
# 我还是学到了 吃这个东西
I have learnt how to eat it properly
# 下次不用你说了
I don’t need your guidance next time.
# 把它掰开
Just break it up like this
# 我晓得啊 这里我倒吃得来了
I know, I know already.
# 没得什么弄得
There’s not too much to eat though.
# 你看她好厉害哦
Look at her, she’s good!
# 多啃就是了
Practice makes perfect!
# 你是老师吃龙虾的老师
You are the master in eating crayfish
# 你一个人吃5斤这里10斤一个人要吃好多哦
You can finish like 2.5 kg already by yourself (we only have 5 kg here)
# 好啦下次再给你们分享做法
Alright I will share more cooking details next time.
# 这个又没什么吃方得了
This one is so small.
# 今天是切这个黄瓜翻车了
I screwed up a little bit while cutting the cucumbers
# 切到一下手
I cut my finger a little bit.
# 然后所以今天有很多东西没拍到
So we didn’t film enough details today.
# 下一次给你们拍一个更加仔细的
I will come back with more details next time.